天堂陌影
是
Yeah.
你好，洛特阿姨
Oh. Hello, Aunt Lotte.
别跟我用匈牙利语讲话
Don't speak to me in Hungarian, please.
不，我没听他们讲过..... 十年了
No, I haven't heard from them... not for 10 years.
我收到你的信了
Yeah, I got your letter.
请讲英语
Speak English, please.
是的，我的小堂妹艾娃
Yeah, my little cousin Eva.
是的 我知道她要到这来 而且要过夜
Yeah, I know. She's gonna come here, and she's gonna stay overnight.
她什么时候来？
When is she coming?
今天？直接从布达佩斯来？
Today? Straight from Budapest today?
噢 不行！
Oh, no!
不行 我没同意这事
No, I never agreed to that.
我不可能照顾她整整十天
I can't possibly babysit her for 10 days.
我的整个生活都会被扰乱的
No, look. It's disrupting my whole life.
我没有将自己看成 这个家庭的成员.
I don't even consider myself a part of the family.
你明白吗？
Do you understand?
好吧 我很抱歉你得住院
No, I'm sorry you have to go into the hospital.
是的
Yeah.
再见啦 - 好啦，再见
Good Bye. - Okay. Bye-bye.
再见
Bye.
该死的
Damn it. Sh...
§ I put a spell on you §
§ Because you're mine §
§ Stop the things you do §
§ I ain't lyin' §
§ Yeah, I can't stand §
§ Whoo §
§ No runnin' around §
§ I can't stand §
§ I know you're puttin' me down §
§ I put a spell on you §
§ Because you're mine §
§ Whoa, yeah §
§ Whoa §§
来了
Yeah?
天啊！
Jesus.
你好！我是艾娃 摩尔纳.
Hello. I'm Eva Molnar.
是的，没开玩笑
Yeah, no kidding.
你是贝拉 摩尔纳？
Are you Bela Molnar?
不是
No.
我曾经是.  你要叫就叫我威利  行吗？
I used to be. Call me Willie if you gotta call me something, all right?
别讲匈牙利语
Oh! Don't speak Hungarian at all.
只讲英语，懂吗？你在这里只能讲英语
Only English, all right, while you're here? Only English.
好吧，请进
Yeah, well, come in!
明天我要乘火车 去俄亥俄州的克利夫兰
Tomorrow I must go to Cleveland in Ohio by train.
呃 我想 明天你不能去那儿
Yeah, well, you can't go to Cleveland in Ohio tomorrow.
洛特阿姨要住院十天
Aunt Lotte has to go into the hospital for 10 days.
因此，今晚你可以待在这  十天之后你可以随便去哪
So you can stay here tonight, and I don't know what you're gonna do after that.
十天？- 是的
For 10 days? - Yeah.
十天？
Ten days?
威利?
Willie?
威利？
Willie？
喂？
Hello?
他在睡觉
Yes, he's sleeping.
什么？你说什么？
What? Excuse me?
我不明白你说的
I don't understand.
我是他的堂妹
Yeah, I am his cousin.
我真的是他的堂妹
I am really his cousin.
请再讲一遍？
Excuse me?
可以讲慢点吗？
Could you speak a little slower, please?
是，克盖？
Yes. Courguy?
我来告诉他
Okay. I will tell him.
谁打了电话来？
Who rang?
没错，电话响了
Yes, the telephone rang.
不是 我是想问 是谁打来的电话？
No, I mean, who was on the phone?
他说他叫克盖
Courguy. He said his name was Courguy.
什么？- 他自称克盖
What? - He said his name was Courguy.
我不认识叫克盖的人
I don't know anybody named Courguy.
他是这样称呼自己的
That's what he said his name was.
该死 别回我的电话，好吗？
Don't answer my fuckin' phone, all right?
克盖
Courguy.
艾娃？你要出去？- 是的
Hey, Eva? You goin' out? - Yeah.
从这边向南走两个街区就是克林顿街
Look, um, Clinton Street is two blocks south of here.
我是不会走过克林顿街南边的
I wouldn't go any further south than Clinton Street.
为什么？- 那里非常危险
- Why? - It's really dangerous there.
我能照顾自己
I can take care of myself.
听我说，你刚来，你不知道在这个城市会发生什么
Man, listen. You come here, you don't know what's going on in this city.
你以前没有来过这 你来了 住在我的公寓
You never been here before. You come and stay in my apartment.
我甚至不希望你来 现在你说“我知道会发生什么”？
I don't even want you here, and you're just, like, "Yeah, I know what's going on."
该死 你真觉得我们很熟？
You think we're so motherfucking together.
我要自己去
I'm going alone.
随你 你自己去吧
Oh. Okay. Go alone.
你确定不要“电视快餐”吗
You sure you don't want a TV dinner?
我还不饿
Yes. I'm not hungry.
这东西为什么叫“电视快餐”
Why is it called "TV dinner"?
就是说你应该 在看电视的时候 把这东西吃掉
Um, you're supposed to eat it while you watch TV.
电视 - 我知道什么是电视
Television. - I know what a TV is.
这肉是哪来的
Where does that meat come from?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我问这是什么肉
What does that meat come from?
我想这是牛肉
I guess it comes from a cow.
牛肉？
From a cow?
但它看起来甚至不像肉
It doesn't even look like meat.
艾娃，别惹毛我，行吗
Eva, stop bugging me, will you?
这就是我们美国人的食物
You know, this is the way we eat in America.
我吃过肉了，我吃过土豆了
I got my meat, I got my potatoes...
我吃过蔬菜，我吃过甜点
I got my vegetables, I got my dessert.
但我不用洗碗
And I don't even have to wash the dishes.
谁呀？
Yeah.
嗨- 嘿 威利
Hi. - Hey, Willie. Hey!
嗨，老兄，你呢 - 棒极了
- Hey, man. How you doin'? - Pretty good.
I didn't know you had company.
我不知道你这还有别人
这是我堂妹- 什么？
- That's my cousin. - Yeah?
她从匈牙利来
She's from Hungary.
她很可爱嘛 - 闭嘴，哥们儿
- She's cute. - Shut up, man.
嗨，- 嗨
Hi. - Hi.
我叫艾迪 - 艾娃
I'm Eddie. - Eva.
过得怎么样 - 还行吧
- How do you do? - Okay.
从匈牙利来？
Hungary?
是的. - 那 呃 你在纽约 呃 待了很久吗
- Yeah. - You been here in, uh, New York, uh, long?
只待了两天.
For two days only.
喜欢纽约吗？- 嗯
You like it? - Yes.
我要去克利夫兰市一个星期
I'm going to Cleveland in about a week.
克利夫兰市是一个很漂亮的城市
Cleveland. It's a beautiful city.
是吗？是的，
- Yes? - Yeah.
那有一个很漂亮的大湖 你会喜欢的
It's got a big, beautiful lake. You'll love it there.
你去过那里吗？- 不 没去过
Have you been there? - No, no.
谁跑第二轮
Who's running in the second race?
呃 有“印度捐赠人”, “面朝音乐”...
Ah, we have Indian Giver, Face the Music...
还有Inside Dope, Off the Wall, Cat Fight, Late Spring...
Inside Dope, Off the Wall, Cat Fight, Late Spring...
这里有Passing Fancy 还有, 呃, “东京故事”
Passing Fancy and, uh, Tokyo Story.
东京故事  - 这我喜欢听
Tokyo Story. It's what I like to hear.
哥们 别坐在我的衬衫上 - 抱歉
Get off my shirt, man. - Oh, sorry.
第三轮都有谁？
Who's in the third?
“音乐与舞蹈”，Last McCoy, the Real McCoy...
Song and Dance, Last McCoy, the Real McCoy...
“公平交易“，女性触觉”
Square Deal, Female Touch.
我看好”女性触觉“. - 我不想赌这场
- That's a good one. Female Touch. - I don't want to bet on that race.
带艾娃去吗？不
- Are we gonna take Eva? - No, we're not gonna take Eva.
他很烦我
He bugs me.
你应该和我们一起去. 你会玩得很开心
You should come with us. You'd have a good time.
那好玩吗？- 哦 很有意思的
- Is it nice? - Oh, it's fun, yeah. Yeah.
我准备好了
Okay. I'm ready.
我们为什么不带艾娃去？- 嗯？
- Why don't we take Eva with us? - Huh?
为什么不带艾娃去？
Why don't we take Eva?
我可不想带艾娃去. - 她会玩得很开心
- I don't want to take Eva with us. - She'd have a good time.
艾娃，听好了 别惹麻烦  在我不在的时候乖乖待在这里
Look, Eva, stay out of trouble, all right? Just stay here while I'm out.
好吗？
All right?
走吧
Let's go, man.
我们为什么不带她去？
Why don't we take her with us?
拜托，老兄
Come on, man.
再见 - 到时候见 艾娃
Bye. - See you later, Eva.
我们会再见面的
I'll see you again sometime.
The ball is in the air.
It's pass interference, and the ball will be spotted at the 15.
所以，你看到那个拿到球的人了吗？- 唔嗯...
- So, you see the guy who's got the ball? - Mm-hmm.
那就是四分卫.
That's the quarterback.
他可将球传给跑位的人 或者直接传球到前场
He can either hand off to one of the runners or he can pass it downfield.
他就有点像 呃 你知道的
It's kind of like, you know, he's, um...
The ball is in the air, just out of the left...
他像一个将军一样，控制着进攻
He's, uh, like the general, you know. He's sort of like- he's in charge of the offense.
四分卫控制着整个进攻
The quarterback is in charge of the whole offense.
That'll make it first down, Cincinnati, at the San Francisco 15.
Clock running.
那如果让这个四分卫做后卫，他该怎么办
So what does the quarterback do when he becomes the defense?
什么
What?
如果他的队伍要防守， 那四分卫要怎么做
What does the quarterback do when his team becomes the defense?
四...四...
The quarter...
四分卫绝对不可能打后卫的
The quarter... The quarterback's not on the defense ever. Uh...
我不知道该怎样向你解释
I... Uh, I don't know how to explain this to you.
That's a close one.
还是看比赛好啦
Just watch the game.
The closest men were two offensive linemen.
我觉得这比赛很蠢
I think this game is really stupid.
That really shouldn't be a penalty for throwing the ball away.
The Bengals get a break here.
Watch this pass rush.
那个记录是克雷尔音乐家 在五个世纪前创造的
That recording was made by Krell musicians a half a million years ago.
现在 如果你跟我来 我可以给你看看他们 遗留下来的一些古器物
Now if you will follow me, I will show you some of their other remaining artifacts.
克雷尔金属.  试试你的冲击波吧，指挥官
Krell metal. Try your blaster there, Commander.
此处应该已经被熔化了
This spot should be molten.
可是它甚至没有发热，不是吗？
It's not even warm, huh?
也没有一点放射性
And no trace of radioactivity.
安静，在那
Shh. In there.
喂，我有事和你们商量
Hello, Mae. I've got a bone to pick with you.
- Ouch! Oh! - Uh-huh!
你有吸尘器吗？
Do you have a vacuum cleaner?
什么？这里灰尘太多了
- What? - It's really dirty in here.
你有吸尘器吗？- 你要什么？吸尘器？
Do you have a vacuum cleaner? - What do you want? A vacuum cleaner?
别打开
Don't open that. Oh, man.
吸尘器在床下
The vacuum cleaner's under the bed.
我叫别打开.把下面关上
I told you not to open that. Close the bott...
先关下面，再关上面
The bottom one first, and then the top one.
它在床下 - 在哪？噢
It's under the bed.  - Where? Oh.
威利，你能帮我换个集灰包吗？
Willie, can you help me change the bag?
里面好像塞满了东西
It looks full.
它肯定没有问题 只是有好几年没有用了
I'm sure it's fine. It hasn't been used in years.
里面好像很脏 - 艾娃
It looks dirty. - Eva.
是吗
Are you sure?
你知道吗. 你不该这样说 比如 这说法太正式了
You know, you don't say- Like, it's really too formal to say...
”我想清洁地板 我想使用吸尘器“
"I want to vacuum the floor. I want to use the vacuum cleaner."
噢 那你会怎么说
Oh. What do you say?
呃 你可以这么说 ”我想让这条鳄鱼窒息“
Well, you say, um, "I want to choke the alligator."
所以，如果有人进来，你知道的， 你就说”我正在窒息一条鳄鱼“
So if somebody comes in here, you know, you say, "I'm choking an alligator."
好吧
Okay.
”我正在窒息一条鳄鱼“
I am choking the alligator right now.
没什么
Ba-boo, ba-boo. Nothing.
嗨，威利
Hi, Willie.
你好啊，艾娃
Hello, Eva.
你们玩的怎么样 - 挺高兴的
- How're you doing? - Okay.
你们从哪弄来这些东西
Where'd you get all that stuff?
我还以为你身上没有钱
I thought you didn't have any money.
我没有为这些东西花钱
I got this stuff with no money.
这是特意给你的
This one is especially for you.
电视快餐
TV dinner.
谢谢
Thanks.
你做得对，孩子
Whew! Ah, you're all right, kid, I think.
我认为你做得对，孩子
I think you're all right, kid.
他妈的
Damn.
所以我是把整个下午都耗在这了
So I've been losing all afternoon here.
我赢了 - 是的
- I've been winning. - Yeah.
§ I know you're puttin'me down §
§ I put a spell on you §
§ Because you're mine §
§ Whoa, yeah §
§ Whoa §
哦，你好
Oh, hi.
§ Stop the things you do §
他妈的，那是什么？
What the fuck is that?
§ I ain't ly... - §§
我真讨厌那种音乐
I really hate that kind of music.
是尖叫的杰 霍金斯. 他很狂野，因此惹毛你了
It's Screaming Jay Hawkins, and he's a wild man, so bug off.
所以 呃
So, uh...
我给你买了点东西
um, I got something for you.
什么东西？- 一件礼物
What is it? - It's a present.
礼品？-嗯
Present? - Mmm.
谢谢
Thanks.
是什么？
What is it?
是件衣服？是的
- It's a dress? - Yeah.
噢 谢啦
Oh, thank you.
我觉得有点丑，你不觉得吗？
I think it's kind of ugly. Don't you?
不丑啊.  这是我买的
No. I bought it.
为什么不试穿一下？
Why don't you try it on?
我不怎么穿这种风格的
I don't really wear this style.
呃 你知道的，你既然来了这里 就应该穿得像个本地人
You... You know, you come here, you should dress like people dress here.
那就等一下，我会去试穿
I'll try it on... later.
嗨，给我留几盒切斯特菲尔德烟
Hey. Leave me some Chesterfields.
我可以到克利夫兰市买吗？
Can I get them in Cleveland?
当然
Yeah, yeah. You can get 'em in Cleveland.
那里买的抽起来也不错吧 像这里一样？
They taste good there, like here?
所有切斯特菲尔德香烟都一样.  - 是吗？
- It's the same Chesterfields. - Yeah?
全美国都一样. 没错
All over America, yeah.
好吧
All right.
你真的不要我跟你去车站吗？
So, you're sure you don't want me to come with you to the station?
是的，我自己去就行了
Mm-hmm. I would like to go by myself.
哦
Oh.
那好吧 照顾好自己
So, I don't know. Take care of yourself.
我会的
Okay.
再见，威利
Good-bye, Willie.
所以.. 艾娃 - 嗯？
-So, Eva... - Yeah?
我不知道，或许我们还会再见面的
Uh, I don't know. Maybe I'll see you again sometime.
嗯 或许吧
Yeah, maybe.
噢 嗨
Oh. Hi.
艾娃？
Eva.
我很讨厌这件衣服
This dress bugs me.
我要去克利夫兰市了
I'm leaving. I'm going to Cleveland.
那是个漂亮的城镇
It's a beautiful town.
嗯 再见
Well, good-bye.
嗯 见到你真高兴
Well, it was nice meeting you.
嗯 我也是
Yeah, it was nice meeting you too.
来了
Yeah?
嗨，威利 - 嗨 老兄
- Hey, Willie. - Hey, man.
怎么样？我很好
- How are you doin'? - I'm all right.
你还好吗？
How are you doin'?
我见到艾娃了. 她要去克利夫兰市吧？
I saw Eva. She's going to Cleveland, eh?
她已经去了
- She's gone, man. - Oh, yeah.
你看到 呃 我给她买的那件衣服了？- 啊 看到了
- You see the... the dress I got her? - Oh, yeah.
很漂亮吧？- 当然了 很漂亮
- It's beautiful, right? - Yeah. Beautiful dress.
喝啤酒吗？好吧
- You want a beer? - Yeah.
我赌平局
I'll bet a deuce.
平局
And a deuce.
我已经够了
Enough for me.
我同意
I'm in.
我也同意
给我三个
Give me three.
我就这些吧
I'll stay with these.
给我一个
Give me one.
庄家两个
Dealer takes two.
我赌一英镑
All right. I'll bet a pound.
Your five, and five.
And five more. - Oh, I like this.
I'm in. - I'm in.
满堂红
Full house.
你在唬人吧  - 噢 老兄 我也这么觉得 相信我
- I thought you were bluffing. - Oh, man. So did I, believe me.
老兄 我根本不信有这种事
You know, I don't believe this, man.
每次艾迪做庄，威利都赢
Every time Eddie deals, Willie wins.
每次威利做庄，威利也赢
Every time Willie deals, Willie wins.
好像是这样 - 你说什么
Hey, that's right. - What are you saying?
每五手牌，你都要赢两手
I'm saying that you're winning two out of every five hands...
他们总是同样两手牌
and they're always the same two hands!
每五手牌，赢两手. 确实没错
Two out of every five hands. That's right!
你是说我在作弊  - 我可没有这样说
- You sayin' I'm cheatin' then? - I'm not saying you're cheating, man.
那你在说什么？
- Then what are you saying?
我是说，每次我们玩，你都赢...
All I'm saying is that every time we go around, you win...
你是怎么赢这么多钱 老兄？我没有必要听
- What are you doing with the money, man? - I don't have to listen to this.
你这话是什么意思？你在说什么？我在作弊？ 我没必要待在这了
What are you meaning that? - What are you talking? You say I'm cheating? I don't have to stay here.
我们他妈的是在比赛. 肏 把你的手拿开
- We're playing a fucking game here, man! - Get your fucking hands off me!
该死的 你是他的同伙，对吧？
You're his fucking partner too, right?
我根本不认识他 - 我也不会跟你玩牌了
I never met the guy. I'd never playing with you again.
滚吧!
Get out of here, man!
还有你们两个... -什么？你就这么坐着，对吧？
And you two, man... - what? - you just sit there, right?
他走了  你才意识到是吧？
Yeah, he's leaving, yeah. You picked up on that, huh?
你们俩个 就这么坐着 你知道的.
Both of you, man, you just sit there, you know.
你不用替自己狡辩了
You don't fuckin' stick up for yourselves or nothin', man!
我不知道你们他妈的是怎么回事？
I don't know what the fuck is the matter with both of youse.
你让那些畜生 进了你的门，对不对？
And you let those animals in your fucking house too, right?
威利，我们停下来干什么？
Willie, what are we stoppin' in here for?
我们得注意那些家伙. 他们知道有事发生
We gotta watch those guys. They knew somethin' was up.
明天我们乘火车，
Tomorrow we got the track...
然后带着这个 我们做的很好
then with this, we're doin' pretty good.
你姐夫叫什么名字？马克斯？- 是的
What's your brother-in-law's name? Max? - Yeah.
我们能不能从他那里借辆车？ - 我想没问题
Can we borrow a car from Max? - Yeah, I guess.
我们用车来干什么？ 就因为那帮家伙就要离开这里？
Hey, what do we want a car for? You want to leave town because of those guys?
不，那帮人属於轻量级选手. 我不会把他们放在眼
No! Those guys are a bunch of lightweights. I don't care about them.
我只是想离开几天，去看一些不同的东西，你理解吗？
I just want to get out of here and see something different for a few days, you know?
是吗？我不知道
Yeah? I don't know.
嘿 那我们去哪
Hey, where would we go?
嘿，威利，我们去哪？我不知道去哪
Hey, Willie, where would we go? I don't know.
嗨，艾迪
Hey, Eddie.
艾迪
Eddie!
艾迪 ！- 威利，你打算做什么？
Eddie! - Willie! What's that... What do you want?
我什么都不想要
Oh, I don't want nothin'.
我们是要去克利夫兰做件大事吧？
Think this thing's gonna make it to Cleveland?
是的 我们去克利夫兰做件事
Yeah, it'll make it to Cleveland.
如果没成，我们就算了吧  坐巴士回来
Well, if it don't, we'll just ditch it, you know, take a bus back.
马克斯介意吗？- 马克斯能怎么办？
- Won't Max mind? - What can Max do about it?
嘿 在这边停一下  - 为什么？
Hey, pull over over here. - Yeah? Why?
我想跟这家伙谈谈 - 是吗？
I want to talk to this guy. - Yeah?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
先生？
Sir?
先生  - 你想做什么？
- Sir! - What do you want?
你能过来一会儿吗？- 你想做什么？
- Could you come here a minute? - What do you want?
你能过来一会儿吗？我在等巴士
- Could you come over here a minute? - I'm just waiting for the bus.
我想问问方向  - 什么
- I want to ask you directions. - What?
你就过来吧，这样我就不用喊叫
Just come here, so I don't have to yell.
我想知道哪条路通往克利夫兰
Can you tell me which way is Cleveland?
老兄  你别问我了，我得去工作
Give me a break, man. I'm just going to work.
你在哪
Where do you work?
工厂
In a factory.
走吧
Let's go.
我不知道，威利
I don't know, Willie. Ah, the poor guy. God.
可怜的家伙 天哪
Ah, the poor guy. God.
你不应该如此麻烦他
You shouldn't have given him such a hard time.
你能想像在工厂工作的情形吗？
Can you imagine working in a factory?
不，不行
No, I can't.
我现在感觉很糟
Now I feel bad.
啊 别这样
Nah, don't feel bad.
嗨，艾迪.
Hey, Eddie.
别说了 威利
Ah, cut it out, Willie.
威利，等我们到克利夫兰了  我们要住在哪里？
Willie, when we get to Cleveland, where are we gonna stay?
和你堂妹艾娃和阿姨住在一起
With your cousin Eva and, uh, your aunt?
不行
No.
你觉得你堂妹艾娃还记得我吗？
Do you think your cousin Eva will remember me?
艾迪，我很怀疑
I doubt it, Eddie.
我们有多少钱？- 噢 多的很
- How much money we got? - Oh, we got a lot.
很多是多少， 艾迪？- 差不多600块
How much is a lot, Eddie? - We got a lot. We got almost $600.
这就对了，艾迪
You're all right, Eddie.
你知道吗 - 我们现在是一对有钱人
- You know? - We're a couple of rich men now.
太糟了，艾迪，天气正在变坏
This is terrible, Eddie. The weather's getting worse.
看看这些积雪
Look at all the snow here.
你认为我们到了俄亥俄州吗？
You think we're in Ohio yet?
不，我想我们还在宾夕法尼亚州
Nah, I think we're still in Pennsylvania.
威利？什么？
- Say, Willie. - Yeah?
去年我认识你堂妹前
You know, last year, before I met your cousin...
我还不知道 你是从匈牙利或布达佩斯这种地方来的
I never knew you were from Hungary or Budapest or any of those places.
怎么啦？
So what?
我还以为你是美国人
I thought you were an American.
嘿 我和你一样 是美国人
Hey, I'm as American as you are.
克利夫兰市有点像布达佩斯吗？
Does Cleveland look a little like, uh, Budapest?
艾迪，闭嘴
Eddie, shut up.
威利，你睡着了吗？
Willie? You asleep?
我没睡
No, I'm not asleep.
你是谁？- 你好
Who are you? - Hi.
谁在哪 - 是我贝拉
- Who is there? - It's me, Bela.
你不记得我啦？贝拉 摩纳尔，我是你侄子
You don't remember me? Bela Molnar. I'm your nephew.
我十年没有见过你啦  完全想不到是你
No, I don't see you about 10 years. How can I... thinking of you?
见到我高兴吗？见到你太高兴了
- You happy to see me? - I am very happy to see you.
我也是 - 那个小伙子是谁？
Yeah. - Who is that fella?
这是我朋友，艾迪 - 很高兴见到你
This is my friend Eddie. - I'm glad to see you.
你好 - 很高兴见到你
Hi! - I'm glad to see you.
我也很高兴见到你 - 快进来吧
I'm glad to see you too. Come on in.
好 - 请进
Okay. - Come on in.
请进来吧
Come on in.
谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
after these messages.
Research shows that Lysol spray...
My father's gonna kill me!
我们不是真正的匈牙利人
Oh, we're not really hungry.
Goulash, chicken paprika.
你这啤酒吗？
Do you have any beer?
没有
No.
把帽子摘下来
Take off your hat.
刚才在外面 她叫你贝拉？- 别在意这个
She called you "Bela" outside? - Skip it.
噢 谢谢  - 这里欢迎你
- Oh, thanks. - You're welcome.
谢谢你，洛特阿姨
Thank you, Aunt Lotte.
谢谢
Thanks.
味道很好.谢谢你
- It's delicious. - Okay. Thank you very much.
洛特阿姨，你看起来很好 - 谢谢
You're looking really good, Aunt Lotte. - Thank you very much.
艾娃去哪了
Where's Eva?
艾娃在一家热狗摊上班
Eva's working in a hot dog stand.
她什么时候出去的？
What time does she get out?
我们打算 呃 10:00去接她...
We gotta pick her up at, uh... 10:00
行吗？- 嗯 这听起来很好
- Okay? - Yeah, that sounds good.
合你的胃口吗？
You like it?
当然.味道不错
It's very good. Yeah, it's delicious.
谢谢你
Thank you.
As for you, you're confined to campus again for the rest of the semester.
Al, pack your things. I'm calling your father to come get you.
No. No, hold it.
Now, look. Eric is the cause of this whole thing. Now, what's gonna happen to him?
老兄，把汤喝了
Man, eat your soup.
You just haven't figured out the system.
她回来了
Here she comes.
我可以帮你吗？是的
- May I help you? - Yeah.
威利  艾迪
Willie! Eddie!
我就说她还记得我.
I told you she'd remember me.
难以相信!
I can't believe it!
你们到这来做什么？- 呃 我们在旅行 你知道的
What are you guys doing here? - Well, we're on vacation, like, you know.
真的？是的
- Really? - Yeah.
你从纽约来？我们开着车就来了
- You came from New York? - Yeah. We have a car and everything.
真的？- 我们借来的
Oh, yeah? - We borrowed it.
闯祸了吧？
Are you in trouble?
没有
Mm-mmm. No.
你们怎么找到我的？
How did you guys find me here?
我们去过洛特阿姨家  她告诉我们你在这
We went to Aunt Lotte's house, and she told us that you were here.
噢 你们见过她啦？是的
- Oh. You already saw her, huh? - Yeah.
所以 你们能在这多待几天吗？
So, can you stay for a few days?
当然可以 我们可以多待几天 为什么不呢？-嗯 我不知道
Yeah, we could. Why not?- Yeah. I don't know.
见到你们我太高兴了.吃热狗吗？
Oh, I'm so happy to see you. You want a hot dog?
不  - 不了
No, no. - No.
你们吃过饭了，是吗？- 是的
- You already ate, right? - Yeah.
我有点工作要做， 大概需要20分钟的样子
So, I have a little more work to do- like, 20 minutes.
你们可以等我吗？
Can you wait for me? - Mm-hmm.
当然，我们是来接你的
- Yeah. We came to pick you up. - All right. I'll hurry up. Okay?
那好，我会尽快做完的
All right. I'll hurry up. Okay?
好吧 不过我想我们就在车里等吧  我不太喜欢这里
Yeah, but I think we should wait in the car, 'cause I don't like it in here.
我也不喜欢 - 好吧
Neither do I. - Yeah?
好啦，我会尽快的  - 行
- All right, I'll hurry up. - Okay.
刚好20分钟 - 没错
Just 20 minutes. - Yep.
我就跟你说她还记得我  - 嗯 挺好的
I told you she'd remember me. - Well, good.
那好吧...
So, anyway...
行吧  似乎我该去加油站加点油
anyways, it seems it's in the cards that I might be getting a raise down at the gas station.
嘿 你之前说过有一天会和我一起去看电影
Hey, you said you'd go with me to the movies the other night.
你要去看《太空奇才》 还是《奥林匹亚的外国片》
You wanna go see Space Wizards or that foreign flick down at the Olympia?
或者《没有阳光的日子》？
Uh, Days Without Sun. You wanna see that?
我不知道  没有功夫片吗
I don't know. Isn't there a kung fu movie?
我会去找找的.  我们就去看...
I can go and check. We'll see...
嗯 去找找 然后打电话给我，好吗?
Yeah, check and call me up. Okay?
那好   - 嗯 再见
Yeah. - All right. Bye.
再见，艾娃
Bye, Eva.
嗨 - 你好
Hi. - How's it goin'?
你好
How you doin'?
威利，我们现在在克利夫兰市
You know, while we're in Cleveland, Willie
为什么不去看骑士
why don't we go see the Cavaliers?
他们队很糟糕.  - 那又怎么样
Oh, they have a terrible team. - Well, so what?
他们就像0和48或 其它类似的东西一样
They're like 0 and 48 or something like that.
但是，我们现在真是无所事事
Yeah, but we're not doing anything.
那么 你想做些什么
Well, what do you wanna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
我要去看电影
I'm going to the movies.
什么？
What?
你想告诉我什么?
What are you telling me? I know what I wanna do.
我知道自己该做什么
I know what I wanna do.
别我对我指手画脚
No, you don't tell me what to do.
我不是个孩子
I'm not a baby.
我不需要他们来照顾我
I don't need them to babysit me.
不！我根本不需要他们来照顾我  我长大了 好吗？
No, I don't need them to babysit me. I'm a big girl. All right?
嗨，嗨 艾娃
Uh, hey. Hey, hey. Hey, Eva.
为什么我们......
Why don't we just...
洛特阿姨. 听我说 我们可以去
Aunt Lotte? Aunt Lotte, please. Well, we could go to the...
我们特意来看望你.  我们可以一起去看电影，行吗？
We came all this way to see you. We could go to the movies with you, right?
好吧  那会很有趣吧 不是吗？
- All right. Okay. - It could be fun. No?
唉 我真的不明白为何她把我当成一个孩子
All right. I just don't understand why she's treating me like a baby.
什么？我们是去看电影吗？
What... Are we going to the movies?
走吧 小伙子吗
Go ahead! Go ahead.
嗨！我们去看电影吗？
Hey! Are we gonna go to the movies?
A blank screen on which to project the images so ably devised by our friends...
啊 谢谢你载我一程 老兄 - 也谢谢你的招待，比利
Well, thanks for the ride, fellas. - Hey, thanks for paying for us too, Billy.
嘿，艾娃，你愿意和我一起走回家吗？
Okay. Hey, uh, Eva, you wanna walk me to my door?
可以
Okay.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
艾娃，和我一起走回家，好吗
"Eva, do you wanna walk me to my door?"
哥们，我们在这里做什么
Man, what are we doing here?
我不知道
I don't know.
嗨，威利.  - 怎么啦
Hey, Willie. - What?
你想在克利夫兰再多待几天吗？
You wanna stick around much longer here in Cleveland?
怎么了？你想走？- 我不知道  好吧 有点
Why? You wanna go? - I don't know. Yeah. Kind of.
我们明天或后天回去
We could go back tomorrow or the next day or somethin'.
啊 这真的很有趣
You know, it's funny.
你来到一个新地方， 可一切似乎并无不同
You come to someplace new, and everything looks just the same.
艾迪，别开玩笑
No kiddin', Eddie.
呼 这地方可真冷
Whew. It's so cold here.
是啊 我也有点想离开这里
Yeah. I kinda wanna get out of here.
我希望洛特阿姨能讲英语
Wish Aunt Lotte would just speak English.
她很顽固 也很滑稽
She's so stubborn. It's funny.
就和这个家里的其它人一样
Just like the rest of the family.
是的
Yeah.
比利那家伙好吗？
Is that guy Billy all right?
不错， 他是个很好的朋友 - 是嘛
Yeah, he's a nice friend. - Yeah.
跟你讲个笑话，好吗？- 嗯
- Let me tell you a joke. All right? - Mm-hmm.
有三个小伙子，在街上闲逛
There's three guys and they're walking down the street.
一个小伙子向另一个说：“嗨，你的鞋带散了”
One guy says to the other one, "Hey, your shoe's untied."
那个家伙回答：”我知道“
He says, "I know that."
於是，他们继续散步，不对...
And they walk- No.
有两个小伙子在一起逛街
There's two guys, they're walking down the street...
其中一个向另一个说：”嗨，你的鞋带散了“
and one says to the other, "Your shoe's untied,"
那个小伙子回答说：”我知道“ 接着，他们走过了两个街区...
and the other guy says, "I know that." They walk a couple blocks further...
他们碰见一个朋友   他走上前说...
And they see a third friend, and he comes up and says...
呃  你的鞋...
"H... Your shoe's unti...
你的鞋带...
Your shoe's un..."
啊呀 我记不起来了
Uh, I can't remember this joke.
但它真的很不错
But it's good.
我也觉得 - 是啊
I'm sure. - Yeah.
这是个很棒的游戏，不是吗？
It's a pretty good game, right?
我又赢了
I am the winner.
嘿 洛特阿姨，这一轮你已经赢了第三次了
Hey, now, that's three times in a row you've won.
玩纸牌，我运气很好.每次都赢 - 真令人吃惊
I am lucky in card. I win every time. - That's amazing.
让我来接
I'll get it.
你好？嗨
Hello? Hi.
你还好吗 比利？
How you doing, Billy?
我很好
I'm okay.
噢 该死，我忘了  抱歉 我没法...
Oh, yeah. Shit, I forgot. I can't.
我堂哥和他的朋友明天就走了
My cousin and his friend are leaving tomorrow.
今晚我得和他们在一起
I gotta be with them tonight.
不 我真的必须这么做
No, I really should.
噢，比利，你应该能理解吧，嗯？
Oh, come on, Billy! You can understand that, can't you?
别那样对我
Oh, don't give me that.
你知道他们并不重要. 只是他们要走
You know they're not more important. It's just that they're leaving.
别这样，比利
Come on, Billy.
天哪！
God!
下个星期打电话给我， 好吗？我们到时再谈
Just call me next week. All right? We'll talk about it.
好吗？再见
Okay? Bye.
我又赢了  -还没有呢
- I am the winner. - Oh, not again.
你们要看看大湖吗？- 别的都行 这个算了
So, you guys wanna go see the big lake? - Anything but this.
我不知道... - 去吧 艾迪
- Well, I don't know... - Come on, Eddie.
去吧，跳进湖里去 - 噢！洛特阿姨
Go and jump in the lake. - Aunt Lotte!
走吧.
Let's go.
等会儿再和我玩？- 没问题
- You'll play later with me? - Yeah. Yeah.
我真的想赢一次
- I wanna win at least once.
好 我给你一个赢的机会
Okay. I give you a chance, let you win.
一会见 - 再见
We'll see you later. - Okay.
这就是伊利湖
Well, this is it. Lake Erie.
哇，看看这雪
Man, look at all this snow.
噢 太美了
Man, it's... it's beautiful.
它不总是会结冰
It's not always frozen.
因此
So...
知道吗？你们真的很好 这样一路来看我
It was really nice of you guys to come all the way here to see me.
嘿 我们也很高兴你在这里  - 艾迪！
- Hey, it was nice of you to be here. - Eddie!
其实没什么，我们既然出门了 就顺路过来看望你
Oh. We just... You know, we thought we'd come out and see how you were doing.
嗯
Oh.
那有辆拖车
It's kind of a drag here, really.
好吧，再见了
Well, good-bye... again.
再见，艾娃
Good-bye, Eva.
如果你们两个如果在赛马场赢了很多钱
So, if you guys win a lot of money at the racetracks,
别忘了回来”绑走“我
you should come and try to kidnap me.
我们会把你带去一个温暖的地方. 这个地方太糟了
Yeah. We'll take you someplace warm. This place is awful.
再见 - 再见，艾娃
See ya. - Bye, Eva.
再次见到你真高兴
It was nice seeing you again.
我们还剩多少钱？还有许多呢
- How much money we got left? - We got a lot.
数数.
Count it.
嘿 威利，为什么你总是叫我做这做那
Hey, Willie, why are you always telling me what to do?
我觉得如果我不告诉你要做什么， 你就无所事事
It seems like if I don't tell you what to do, you don't do anything at all.
我要知道到底还剩多少钱. 我们还有550块
- I wanna know exactly how much we got. - We got $550 left.
也就是说，我们花了50块
Which means we spent 50.
你去过佛罗里达吗
You ever been to Florida?
佛罗里达可是个漂亮的地方
Florida? Yeah, it's beautiful down there.
嗯？ - 你知道的 洁白的沙滩 比基尼女郎...
- Uh-huh. - You know, white beaches, girls with bikinis.
没错 - 卡纳维拉海角， 迈阿密海滩 - 实在不错
Yeah. - Cape Canaveral, Miami Beach. - That's right.
那有鹈鹕...
They got pelicans down there,
和火烈鸟...  各种各样的怪鸟
那
and flamingos... all those weird birds.
你去过吗？- 不，我从来没去过
You been there? - Nah, I never been there.
艾迪 我觉得你很怪  你知道吗？
You're a jerk, Eddie. You know that?
拜托 又怎么了？
No, come on.
你是说我们去佛罗里达？- 没错啊
What do you say we go down to Florida? - Yeah?
回去吧，带上艾娃，南下去佛罗里达
Yeah. Go back, pick up Eva, drive down to Florida.
我们还有车
We got the car.
没开玩笑？ - 没
- Yeah? You're not kidding? - No.
该死 我们得先回纽约
Well, hell, it beats going back to New York.
好主意
That's a good idea.
我想去佛罗里达.
I'd like to go to Florida.
你没去过，对吧？- 确实
Yeah, you never been there. Right? - No.
下一个出口在哪？
Where's the next exit?
我不希望你把她带走
I don't want you to take her away!
别担心 .我们只是去是度假
Don't worry. We're going on a little vacation.
拜托 我们很快就回来
- Come on! - We'll be back soon.
再见啦
Good-bye.
毫无价值
Good-for-nothing...
你们这些畜生
You son of a bitch.
天哪 我真高兴. 谢谢你们救我出来
God, I'm so glad. Thank you guys for rescuing me.
我不敢相信我们是去佛罗里达.
I can't believe we're going to Florida.
你把你的比基尼带来了吗？- 当然啦
You bring your little bikini along? - Sure.
佛罗里达有鳄鱼吧？
There are alligators in Florida, right?
别放这个 - 这是尖叫的杰的歌
Not that. - It's Screamin' Jay.
真的有够难听
Aw, that's awful.
差劲的是你   他是于我很重要的人
You're the same. He's my main man.
§ 'Cause you're mine §
我喜欢这音乐  - 你喜欢这东西？
- Yeah, I like this. - You like this stuff?
谢谢你支持我，艾迪.
Thank you, Eddie. Back me up.
§ Stop the things you do §
太可怕了
It's horrible.
§ I ain't lyin' §
这是驾驶音乐
This is drivin' music!
很不错
This is nice.
§ Whoo No runnin' around §
我好久没有听过这音乐了
I haven't heard it in a long time.
§ I know you're puttin' me down §
§ I put a spell on you §§
现在，我们真的像游客了
Now we look like real tourists.
非常典型的游客
Pretty classy.
艾娃，等那家伙出来，你就躲起来 直到他回办公室
Eva, I want you to stay down until the motel guy comes out and goes back in his office.
干吗？
Why?
为什么要付三个人的钱？那简直是罚款
Why pay for three people? It's fine.
我记得你们说你们有不少钱.
I thought you guys said you were rich.
嘘！ 躲起来，躲起来
Shh! Get down. Get down.
嗨 你好啊 - 嗨 你好
- Hey. How you doing? - Hi there. How are ya?
好了
Fine.
等他进去  就绕到另一边  3号房
Wait till he goes in and then come around the other side. Room number three.
3号房？- 是的
- Number three? - Yeah.
哥们，我太累了
Man, I'm beat.
我也很累
I'm so tired.
什么？你把花生吃完了？
What, you finished the peanuts?
是的
Yeah.
那你把这罐子带来干嘛？
Then what'd you pack 'em for?
天哪，艾娃
Jesus, Eva!
这个办法就是叫你溜进去. 你知道吗？
The idea was for you to sneak in. You understand?
我不在乎
I don't care.
看起来都一样
This looks familiar.
这是给你的
This is for you.
啊？- 这是给你的
Huh? - This is for you.
噢 不 我不要睡这里
Oh, no. I'm not sleeping on that.
你们两个中的哪一个睡那里吧  我要睡床
One of you guys can sleep there. I'm taking the bed.
我在车等的都快睡着了
I fell asleep waiting out there in the car.
我觉得有点冷.  至少要有一张舒适的床吧
Now I'm cold. I want a comfortable bed, at least.
这可真棒
Amazin'.
嗨，那水闻起来有点怪异
Hey, that water smells funny.
啊啊这 在这种小床上我可没法睡觉
Uh-uh-uh. I'm not gonna sleep on this cot.
你们觉得这很好笑？
You guys think it's so funny?
不，这真的不错 你懂的
No, it's... They're good, you know.
是啊是啊
Yeah, yeah.
我爱你们
I love you guys...
这床真是个”贱货“
but this is a bitch.
我们明天一块去海滩，好吗？
Can we all go to the beach tomorrow?
等我们去完赛马赛之后
After we go to the track.
威利，我们应该看一下赛犬
Hey, Willie, we should check out the dog races.
我不喜欢赛犬这个主意
I don't like the idea of dog races.
安静，我要睡觉了
Be quiet so I can sleep.
睡个好觉，我们才能享受假期，对吧？
Yeah, go to sleep so we can start enjoying our vacation. All right?
好吧
It's okay.
看起来不错 - 我原谅你们
- Looks very nice. - I'll forgive you guys.
嘿，威利，试试一下赛犬吧
Hey, Willie, man, let's check these dog races out.
我有种感觉  我们能赚很多钱
I got a good feeling. I feel like we're gonna make a lot of money.
真的？- 没错，就是这样一种感觉
- Really? - Yeah. It's one of those feelings.
是的
Yeah.
可能是个好主意吧  我不知道
Uh, yeah, maybe it's a good idea. I don't know.
赛狗？
Dog races.
做个好梦.
Have sweet dreams.
晚安
Good night.
威利
Willie?
唔...
Mmm.
威利？艾迪
Willie. Eddie?
该死
Shit.
他妈的！
Fuck!
很好
That's nice.
他们应该留了便签吧
They could have left a note.
该死
Shit.
我他妈的不相信...
Can't fucking believe it.
假期完美开始
Vacation starts great.
他妈的你这一整天跑哪去了  你连个便条都没留
Where the fuck have you been all day? You didn't even leave me a note.
我一个人在这种陌生之地.  一个人都不认识
I'm here alone in the middle of nowhere. I don't know anybody.
你不该做这种事
And you can't do that much...
你走时，应该给我留张便签
leave me a note when you leave.
闭嘴. 艾娃 - 别叫我闭嘴.  这是什么情况？
Shut up, Eva... - Don't tell me to shut up! What is this?
我想我们正在去迈阿密.这里哪都不是
I thought we were going to Miami. This is nowhere.
你说你感觉不错，对吧？- 我感觉不错 威利
- Man, you said you had a good feeling. Right? - I had a good feeling, Willie.
你说好事即将发生 根本不该是这样
It's supposed to mean that something's supposed to happen. Not just like this...
威利，我们不是总能赢
You can't win 'em all, Willie.
发生什么事了？
What's going on?
是你让我去赌赛狗，你现在说：”我们赢不了？“
You take me to dog races and then you say, "You can't win 'em all"?
那是比赛的名称
It's the name of the game!
到底怎么回事？没什么
- What's going on? - Nothin'.
没什么. 只是几乎输光了我们所有的钱
Nothin's going on. Just lost almost all our money.
在赌赛狗上？
At dog races?
你输掉了所有钱？是的
- You lost all the money? - Yeah.
天哪
God.
对不起
I'm sorry.
现在我们怎么办？
What are we gonna do now?
听着，威利，我们先离开这
Look, Willie, let's get outta here.
我们还有50块，我们回纽约去
We got 50 bucks. Let's go back to New York.
我不打算身无分文的回纽约.  - 你想干什么？
- I'm not goin' back to New York with no money. - What do you wanna do?
我想回到赛场去，赌赛马而不是赛犬
I wanna go to the track and I wanna bet on horses, not on dogs.
我就知道你会这样说
I knew you were gonna say something like this.
拜托，我对回到赛场有一种可怕的感觉
Come on! I have this terrible feeling if we go back to the track.
你的感觉没给我们带来任何好处
Your feelings haven't been doing us any good.
这真是个伟大的假期  - 闭嘴，艾娃  走吧
- This is a great vacation. - Oh, shut up, Eva. Come on. Let's go.
随你说什么  威利  随你便
Anything you say, Willie. Anything you say.
艾娃，你在做什么？ - 什么意思？
- Eva, what are you doing? - What do you mean?
你别和我们一起走
- You're not coming with us.
她应该和我们一起走.  她能带来好运.  - 她应该呆在这
- Willie, she should come with us. It'll be good luck. - She's stayin' here.
我认为她应该来，- 她就待在这
- Willie, I think she should come with us. - She's stayin' here!
出去，滚出去！- 对不起，艾娃
- Get out. Get out! - I'm sorry, Eva.
你也出去 出去！  - 我真的很抱歉
- You're the same. Just go. - I'm sorry.
威利，她整天待在汽车旅馆  我们应该带她一起
Willie, she's been in the motel all day. We should take her with us.
你 怪咖 你知道你他妈在哪吗
Yo, little freak, where the fuck you been at, man?
你在哪呢 老兄
- Where you been at, man? - Wha...
肏  你...  你真是个怪咖.  不是吗？
Shit, man... Yo, I mean, you the freak, right?
你带着这帽子，老兄，我看见这个圆顶了  听着
You got the hat on, man. I see the dome piece on your top, man. Listen.
你应该拿着这个，哥们   你让我想起我该死的母亲
You're supposed to take this shit, man. You make me miss my mother fuckin' sniff, man.
拿上这个该死的东西.  告诉兰玫尔，我永远不会再染上这种病
Here, take this shit, man. You tell Rammell that I ain't down with this no more.
你酷吗，你清白吗，你该走了，再见  别激动
You cool? You clean? There you go. Good-bye. Peace.
该死的
No shit.
威利？艾迪
Willie? Eddie?
呼
Whew.
艾娃
Eva?
艾娃？ - 我叫你赌马，而不是赛狗.
- Eva? - I told you horses, not dogs.
你根本不听我的，不是吗
You don't ever listen to me. Right?
赌马 赌马 还是赌马好
Horses. Horses. Definitely horses.
把这个给我 给我 - 你他妈的滚出去
- Give me that. Give me that! - Get the fuck outta here!
快点
Come on.
嘿，天黑了.
Hey, it's dark in here.
你看见"小欢乐"了吗？你看见"小欢乐"了吗？You see Mighty Joy? Did you see Mighty Joy?
是的，他表现得很赞，非常好
Yeah, it was great. He was great.
我想让这地方亮一点
Think I'll shed some light on the situation.
拜托 你个白痴
Come on, you idiot!
艾迪，看看这个 - 那是什么？
Eddie, look at this. - What is that?
天哪，威利！
My God, Willie!
这是什么  上面说的是什么？
What is that? What does it say?
是艾娃留下的.  用匈牙利语写的
It's from Eva. It's in Hungarian.
她说什么？- 这太蠢了.
- What does it say? - Aw, this is stupid.
她去机场了
She's goin' to the airport.
我们不能让她去机场  她真是...
We can't let her go to the airport. She's really...
她的钱怎么来的？
Where did she get all this money?
我不知道钱是哪来的
I don't know where she got the money.
我们应该去找她？- 没错
- We should get her, eh? - Yeah.
好吧.  - 我们走吧
All right, that's fine. Let's go.
我们要离开这个地方对吧
We'll leave this place, eh?
她到底是怎么拿到钱的啊
Where did she get all this money?
你的行李打包好了？ - 对 我准备好了
- Are you packed? - Yeah. I'm ready to go.
这是艾娃的帽子吗？
Is this Eva's hat?
看起来是的
It looks like Eva's hat.
这帽子又是怎么来的？
Where'd she get that hat?
威利，快点 我们离开这里
Willie, come on, will ya? Let's get outta here.
把钱带好了吗？是的 都带上了
- You got all the money? - Yeah, I got everything.
把这个瓶子带上 你不想要你的花生吗？
Take the bottle. - Don't you want your peanuts?
什么花生？里面是空的啊
Why should I want the peanuts? There's nothin' in it.
今天还有一班次去欧洲的航班
Yes, there is one remaining flight to Europe today.
大约45分钟内起飞.  在登机前  你还有很多时间
It leaves in about 45 minutes. You have plenty of time to board.
这是到中欧，布达佩斯的航班
It's a flight to Eastern Europe... to Budapest.
布达佩斯？这是去布达佩斯的航班？
To Budapest? There's a flight from here to Budapest?
是的.
Yes, there is.
只有这一班次到欧洲的航班？ - 这是今天的唯一班次了
That's the only flight to Europe you have? - Well, it's the only flight we have today.
明天倒有几个班次  我可以帮你查一下
We have several tomorrow. I can check on those for you.
晚上12:20有一班次到穆德
Yeah, we have a flight to Madrid at 12:20 p.m.
凌晨2：05有一班次到巴黎
We have a flight to Paris at 2:05.
总之你得等到明天
Although you will have to wait until tomorrow.
今天的航班什么时候起飞?
What time does the plane leave again?
到布达佩斯的航班大约 在44分钟后
The flight for Budapest departs in about 44 minutes.
知道了
Hmm.
What are talking about, sir? Shall I explain it more clearly?
You're a whack-off. You know that?
You have a nice day too, sir.
发生什么事？这个怪人说她在这
- What's goin' on, Willie? - This jerk says she was just here.
她已经上了...他以为她已经上了某个航班
She's got on... He thinks she got on some flight.
那你买票干什么？
So? What do you got a ticket for?
我要买机票  然后上飞机  再把她带下来
I had to buy the ticket so I can get on the plane to take her off the plane.
拿好机票
Here. Take this.
飞机什么时候起飞？
When's the plane?
呃 五分钟内吧 .- 那你动作可要快些
- In, like, five minutes. - You'd better hurry up.
好吧 在车里等我...  - 行 我会回车里
All right, meet me at the car... -  Yeah I'll be back at the car...
十分钟后在车里见我  - 别担心 我会在那里等你
Meet me at the car in 10 min - Don't worry. I'll be there.
没问题吧？ - 嗯 一会见
You all right? Yeah. I'll see you later.
好 - 我就在车里
All right. - I'll be at the car.
乘客们，请注意，
Your attention, please.
世界航空公司904航班  飞往布达佩斯 Royal Airlines Flight 904, nonstop service to Budapest...
即将起飞
is now ready for immediate departure...
请于七号通道，A口登机
gate seven, concourse "A".
威利
Oh, Willie.
我感觉不舒服
I had a bad feeling.
该死的！
Damn.
你到布达佩斯干什么？
What the hell are you gonna do in Budapest?
字幕原作者@致远淡泊   修改者，重制者@uploader0
§ I put a spell on you §
§ Because you're mine §
§ Stop the things you do §
§ I ain't lyin'§
§ Yeah §
§ I can't stand, whoo §
§ No runnin'around §
§ I can't stand §
§ No puttin'me down §
§ I put a spell on you §
§ Because §
§ You're mine §
§ Oh, yeah §
啊
§ Stop the things you do §
§ I ain't lyin'§
§ Ohh, ohh §
§ I love you §
§ I love you anyhow §
§ I don't care if you don't want me §
§ I'm yours right now §
§ I put a spell on you §
§ Because you're mine §
§ Mine §
§ Oh, you're mine §§